http://www.magellangps.com/company/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
We Respect Your Privacy
We are committed to respecting your privacy and recognize your need to protect and manage any personally identifiable information you share with us. We have established this Privacy Policy so that you can understand how we intend to use the information we collect.
Information Magellan Collects
If you access Magellan products and services from one of our web sites, a portable or mobile device, Magellan may collect the following information:
Information you provide to Magellan: it may include personal information such as any information that may be used to identify an individual, including your first and last name, your home or other physical address, your e-mail address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. It may also include a credit card account number, birth date and gender and any information you would like to share. The collection of your information may be necessary to create for example an account on our website or in order for you to be able to purchase our products on our web sites. Our services also offer you the possibility to share information to the public and create a publicly visible profile to share your activity, your location, your photo or other information.
Information from your use of our services or devices: it may include location data (when you use a location-enabled Magellan service, we may collect and process information about your location), device information (such as product model, operating system), log information (such as device event information, system activity, hardware settings, failures and crashes logs, internet protocol address, search queries, details of how you used our services
How do we use information we collect?
We may use information that we collect to fulfill your requests for our products and services, to communicate with you and assist you with any question you have about an order or a product, to offer you other products and services, to display content and advertising customized to your interests and preferences, to display, with your consent, your publicly visible profile information to others, to assist us in the development or improvement of our products and services, to cooperate with government officials or parties in litigation under process of law or regulation, or as otherwise required or permitted by law, to protect the security or integrity of the products or services and to protect against legal liability. Personal information may be locally stored on your device. We may provide information that we collect to third party service providers across borders and from your country to other countries around the world to help us deliver programs, products, information and services. Service providers are also an important means by which we maintain our web sites, mailing lists and other services. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third party service providers are obligated to protect personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We do not intend to transfer personal information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Magellan's behalf unless such transfer is (i) legally required, (ii) for the purpose indicated in this paragraph, or (iii) in connection with a merger or acquisition of Magellan. It is against our policy to sell collected personal information.
You Have a Choice
You may choose whether or not to provide your information. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still use most of our web sites and services and access certain information, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers and services. Some mandatory service messages are required for use of certain products and services and are not subject to opt-out. If you use one of our services that let you share information with others, we offer you different options on sharing and removing your content. For such services, you can control who you share information with, modify and adjust your profile and take information out of these services. You may also opt to receive certain services such as electronic newsletters or receive notices of promotions and special offers by e-mail. By completing a registration form on the web site you will be opting-in. We will offer you the opportunity to opt-out or unsubscribe to electronic newsletters or mailing lists at any time.
We Use Cookies
Some of our web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used to collect information about web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may recall personal information previously provided by a web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Tracking technologies record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. We use cookies and other tracking technologies so that we can improve our web site and your web experience. We may also analyze information for trends and statistics. We do not generate e-mail lists from cookies.
How We Secure Your Information
Wherever your information may be held within Magellan or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the personal information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. We use firewalls, encryption technologies (such as SSL) and physical security measures in order to prevent unauthorized use of personal information. Only employees of Magellan or our third-party agents who need the information to perform a specific task (for example, order processing and fulfillment) will be granted access to personal information. Credit card account information is used only for a single transaction and is retained only as a part of the applicable order. It is not maintained together with other personal information on our web site.
Accessing and updating your Information
When you do provide us with personal information, we want it to remain accurate. Where we collect personal information from you, we intend to provide a means for you to access, update or correct that information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your personal information via our Contact web page located at http://www.magellangps.com/contact/ and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your personal information that we hold as soon as practicable. If you delete information from our services, we may not delete residual copies from our servers and may not remove information from our backup systems.
Links
Magellan web sites contain links to other web sites. Magellan is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content, accuracy or opinions expressed on such web sites or any link contained in such site. Our Privacy policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including other sites linked from our services. Links are provided as a convenience and are not investigated, monitored or checked by us for accuracy or completeness. Providing a link on our site does not imply approval or endorsement of the linked site by us.
Children's Privacy
Our websites are not structured to attract children. We do not intend to collect personal information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.
Your Consent
By using Magellan web sites, products and services, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to our use of your information for the purposes given where the information is collected. Should the Privacy Policy change, we intend to ensure that changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes on this web page, and if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including for certain services, email notification).
Contact Information
If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us via our Contact web page. We will address any issue or complaint to the best of our abilities by contacting the person who made the complaint as soon as possible.
Home
>
COMPANY
>
Privacy Policy
